NATALIA MALVICINO



WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Buenos Aires, Argentina (7) /Aafterlife17

aafterlife17.github.io

(2) +54 9 11 6365-4880

in /nataliamalvicino 🖂 natalia.malvicino@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I consider myself a creative, determined and organized person, searching for new challenges and to broaden my knowledge.

I have more than a year's experience working as a Web Developer and a Graphic Designer, currently studying to become a Frontend Developer

SKILLS

Web Development

Graphic Design

Languages

HTML₅ Advanced Illustrator Advanced English Advanced CSS3 Advanced Adobe XD Advanced JavaScript Intermediate Photoshop Intermediate WordPress Intermediate

TOOLS























GIT

Google **Fonts**

Figma

Font Awesome Canva

Icon Scout Bootstrap

Adobe Plunker Color

Stack Blitz

Swiper

EDUCATION

System Engineer

Web Designer/ **UI Designer**

Humanities and Social Science

Buenos Aires University 2021 - Present

Educación IT Institute 2018-2020

Carlos Steeb High School 2008 - 2012

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Freelance 2020 - Presente

Website development for multiple clients using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Wordpress.

Graphic Designer

Tekno Homes S.A. 2017 - 2018

Web design, working alongside the developer, web tests. Arrangement of presentation folders, display plotters, banners, product sheets, advertising campaigns. Management of the company's social networks. Translations.

Graphic Designer

Punto & Papel 2016 - 2017

Daily usage of Adobe software to make prints, display plotters, personal business cards, wedding invitations, etc.